[{"answer": "Why?   Do you have a report due", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Okay, let's start with the free messages outside the that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "God, that would be weird it that situation presented itself tonight, huh", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Dude, I don't know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, but I got cou", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Okay, you don't have to stop, I'm invisible, I'm not here.", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.  But ah, hey, oh, somebody's off the phone, how 'bout a glass of wine by the fire, I could get it going again", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Come on Rach, you don't have what, ten minutes", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend you're not listening to me, I don't have time to stop", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't have ten minutes!", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come on Rach, you don't have what, ten minutes", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What?   my friend, does she have ten minutes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't have ten minutes!", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Hey, my friend!!!  I told you I don't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "But I told you, I didn't have the time", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Wh, my friend what do you want from me?  You want me, you want me to quit my job so you can feel like you have a girlfriend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Wh, my friend what do you want from me?  You want me, you want me to quit my job so you can feel like you have a girlfriend", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Just a job", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Okay, it's not, it's not", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh I'm, I'm making this too hard.  Okay, what do you want me to do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh I'm, I'm making this too hard.  Okay, what do you want me to do", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Okay, okay, fine, you're right.  Let's ah, let's take a break,  let's cool off, okay, let's get some frozen yogart, or something..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't know, I don't know.  Urrrgh! Look, maybe we should take a break", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No.  A break from us", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, can I talk to you behind my menu, please.   What are you doing", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah but, my friend is so interested in you, that my friend and I haven't been able to say two words to each other", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Ah, that's okay, thanks", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Look, I don't feel like dancing, I feel like having a drink.  Okay", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Uh,  plate", "docId": "315rrtb.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Plate.  Plate.  Plate", "qsentId": 30}]